https://victorson.com/privacy-policy/

Thank you for visiting www.victorson.com (our “Site”). We appreciate the opportunity to interact with you on the Internet and are committed to protecting and safeguarding your privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to inform you about the types of information we might collect about you when you visit our Site, how we may use that information and whether we disclose that information to anyone.
What Information We Collect and How We Use It
Any information we collect on our Site generally falls into the Personally Identifiable Information category.
Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that lets us know specifically who you are. In general, you can visit our Site without telling us who you are or revealing any Personally Identifiable Information.
Sharing Your Information
Except as disclosed in this Privacy Statement, we do not sell, trade, rent, or otherwise retransmit any Personally Identifiable Information we collect online unless we have your permission. Any Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us will be used for the purpose of dealing with you and retained in hard copy form as well as within our database system.
From time to time, we may be required to provide Personally Identifiable Information in response to court order, subpoena, or government investigation. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. We may release Personally Identifiable Information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Limited Warranty or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves.
Links To Other Web Sites
Links to third-party Web sites may be provided solely for your information and convenience, or to provide additional information for various other goods and services. If you use these links, you will leave our Site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those Web sites linked to our Site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit.
Changes To This Statement
Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Statement will be posted here on our Site and the date of the newest version posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any Personally Identifiable Information at our Site, to see if this Privacy Statement has changed.
By using our Site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Statement in effect at the time of use.
Contact Us
If you have any concerns about our use of your information or about this Privacy Statement, please send an e-mail to vainc@victorson.com. We will make every reasonable effort to address your concerns and remedy any problems you bring to our attention.
This Privacy Statement was last revised on August 28, 2015.
Get our app
Search for:
Connect with Us
Recent Posts
International Medical Group – Travel Insurance Plans
Another Positive Step For HIV-Positive People
Life expectancy in the world – How it has changed over the last 200 years
Genworth Reprices NY LTC Policy
Keep Up to Date
Click here to sign up for our e-news and updates
View the latest updates on our blog
News TopicsNews Topics
Select Category
Health Insurance
Individual Health Insurance
Individual Insurance
Life Insurance
Long Term Care
News
Member
DisclaimerThis website is not for consumer use. This site and its contents are strictly for the use of agents licensed with Victorson Associates, Inc. Please click here to read the full disclaimer.
